字幕组
ZiMuZu.tv
我叫巴里·艾伦
My name is Barry Allen,
是现今世上速度最快的人
and I'm the fastest man alive.
在外人看来
To the outside world,
我只是个普通的鉴证专员
I'm an ordinary forensic scientist,
但在尖端科研实验室的朋友们的帮助下
but secretly, with the help of my friends at S.T.A.R. Labs,
我秘密地打击犯罪  寻找跟我一样的超能力者
I fight crime and find other meta-humans like me.
在我打败极速并拯救了多元宇宙后
After defeating Zoom and saving the multiverse,
我跑回到了过去
I ran back in time and created
创造出了另一条时间线  闪点
the alternate timeline Flashpoint.
我恢复了时间线原来的状态
I restored the timeline to how it was,
但发现有些事却不一样了
only to find things weren't as I left them.
我给我们的世界带来了新的威胁
I brought new threats to our world,
而我是唯一来得及阻止他们的人
and I'm the only one fast enough to stop them.
我就是  闪电侠
I am The Flash.
《闪电侠》前情回顾
Previously on "The Flash"...
这是个非常棒的约会  闪电侠
This has been a really amazing date, Flash.
塞西尔  谢谢你能来
Cecile, thanks for stopping by.
我愿为我最爱的警探赴汤蹈火
Hey, anything for my favorite detective.
你恢复了时间线  却发现事情都变了
You restored the timeline, and things were different?
没错
Exactly.
杰西  你是极速者吗
Jesse, you're a speedster.
我回来后  一切还是变了样
When I came back, things weren't the same.
你是说我们变了
You mean people.
对
Yeah.
中城布鲁姆
实业公司 正门
三年前
怎么样
How do I look?
好看多了
Better.
多少钱
How much?
还要问这种问题吗
Do we really need to ask that question?
我们那份没那么多
Our take wasn't that big.
够多了
Big enough.
你唯一要问的问题是
But the only question you should be asking is,
你的美颈上想带一颗多大的钻石
what size rock you want dangling from this beautiful neck?
你的吻让我神魂颠倒
A kiss from you makes my world spin.
你就会甜言蜜语
You're so full of it, you know that?
说实话
I got to be honest.
我一直不明白  这个
I never understood... this.
不过就像我妹妹说的
But like my sister says,
你总是可以装样子唬唬人
anyone can stoop over and pick up nothing.
你想怎么样  史纳特
What do you want, Snart?
我跟你俩说了先不要用你们那份钱
I told you two to sit on your cut for a while,
等风波过去了再说
until things cool down.
有些人喜欢花掉
Some of us like to actually spend the cash
自己工作挣来的钱
we get from these jobs.
从我这挣的就不行
Not when it's from the ones with me.
这不是你一个人的功劳
You didn't pull 'em off yourself.
没有我们  你还在砸酒馆呢
Without us, you'd still be kicking down liquor stores.
我觉得你是花了太多时间
I think you've spent too much time
盯着镜子中的自己了
staring at yourself in the mirror,
因为你对现实的理解都有点扭曲了
because your perception of reality is a bit warped.
你应该懂规矩的
You know the rules.
我才不管你的狗屁规则呢
I don't give a damn about your rules,
我也不会低调
or laying low.
这座城市里没人能阻止我们
There's no one in this city who can stop us.
包括你  史纳特
Including you, Snart.
听上去你们的意思是想分道扬镳了
It sounds to me like you're saying you want out.
是的
Guess so.
你们要是想分
Well, if you're out...
那就分吧
you're out.
不要
No!
你输了  斯卡德
You lost, Scudder.
山姆
Sam!
走
Go.
快走
Go!
中城布鲁姆
实业公司 正门
山姆
Sam?
帮我一把
Give me a hand here.
现在
还有一个月就要展示了  把东西都清理出去
Demo starts in a month. Get everything out of here.
怎么回事
The hell?
史纳特在哪
Where's Snart?
闪电侠
第三季
第四集
这是铁山监狱里的监控视频
This is from a security camera inside Iron Heights.
法证分析表明这段视频是真的
Forensic analysis indicates that the footage is genuine,
没有被编辑过
no evidence of tampering.
确定是炼金术博士干的吗
And we're pretty sure this is Doctor Alchemy that did this?
克拉里斯临死前说的
The last thing Clariss said before he died.
除非是别人杀了他
Unless someone else killed him.
比如有心灵遥感和会隐身的超能力者
Like a meta with telekinesis or cloaking abilities.
我们地球上这两种人都有
We've got both on our Earth.
那我们现在该怎么做
So what do we do now?
我们中城警局的超能力者专家
Our meta-human specialist at CCPD,
朱利安·艾伯特  他喜欢单打独斗
Julian Albert, he prefers to work alone,
不过我了派人去探听他的调查进展
but I got feelers out on his investigation.
我现在去看看他有没有什么发现
I'm gonna go there now and see if he dug up anything.
好的
All right.
好吧  在那之前你们想训练一下吗
Okay, well, until then, you guys want to train?
现在我们得考虑回到我们的地球了
Well, now, we have to think about getting back to our Earth.
我们已经来这够久了
We've been here long enough.
可我还要很多东西要学
I've still got a lot to learn.
你说的  不是我说的
Your words, not mine.
我
I...
好吧
fine.
如果你想训练
Well, if you want to train,
那我们就训练吧
let's train...
极速者风格
speedster style.
厉害  杰西都快和巴里一样快了
Damn, Jesse's almost as fast as Barry.
速度快要达到3马赫了
Velocity's just under Mach 3.
心率每分钟100  她的体征都很正常
Heart rate, 100 BPMs. Her vitals are normal.
是的  我们已经知道了
Yeah, no, we already know all that.
西斯科  我们需要测试她的条件反射
Cisco, we need to test her reflexes.
我们能测试她的条件反射吗
Can we test her reflexes?
耐心点  哈里  耐心点
Patience, Harry, patience.
要是有人能教给杰西怎么控制神速力
If anyone's gonna teach Jesse the ways of the Speed Force--
-肯定是巴里  -谢谢
- It's Barry. - Thank you.
好吧  刚才不是很有英雄范
Okay. Well, that wasn't very heroic.
是的
Nope.
不过你应该从中学到点东西
But there is a lesson in there somewhere.
学什么
What's that?
有能力和做得准之间的差别
The difference between having powers and having precision.
什么意思
Well, what do you mean?
要打败这些超能力者
I mean, it's gonna take more than speed
需要的不止是速度
to take down some of these metas.
要运用脑子  先发制人
You got to think, anticipate.
当你走进一个新环境时
When you enter a new environment,
要仔细查看每一个角落
you got to case every inch of it.
绝对不能鲁莽行事
You never run in blind.
天呐
Oh, my God.
我变成奥利弗了
I've become Oliver.
也许我们应该在这多待一阵
Maybe we should stay a little bit longer.
我想也是
Yeah, I guess so.
掌控超能力是需要时间的  杰西
It's gonna take some time to master your powers, Jesse.
-你会掌握窍门的  -我知道  谢谢
- You'll get the hang of it. - Yeah, I know, thanks.
既然我会在这多待一阵
Well, since I will be here for a while,
要不要一起出去玩玩
do you want to get out of here?
-去哪  -有所谓吗
- Where to? - Does it matter?
不许有肢体接触
No touching.
我说的待一阵子  不是这样的
Not what I meant by staying longer!
我应该回《中城时报》了
I should probably get back to CCPN.
-好  -今晚见吗
- All right. - I'll see you tonight?
-等不及了  -好
- Can't wait. - Okay.
-哈里  -什么
- Hey, Harry. - Yeah?
你真的一定要走吗
Are you really sure you have to leave?
我的地球上还有很多东西要修复
Just a lot I still have to fix on my Earth.
但是你留在我们的地球上
Yeah, but you know it's more fun
帮忙修复东西会更有意思
when you're here helping us fix stuff on our Earth.
他说得对
He is right.
你不在的时候都不一样了
It hasn't been the same without you.
没有哈里森·威尔斯  这个团队就不完整
The team doesn't feel complete without Harrison Wells.
那就改变一下吧
Then change that.
整个多元宇宙里有这么多哈里森·威尔斯
There's a whole multiverse of Harrison Wells
你们都能触手可及
out there at your fingertips.
需要一个吗  那就去找吧
You want one? Let's go get one.
中城警局
我现在想起来了
Yeah, now I remembered it.
谢谢你  迈尔警官
Thank you, Officer Mayer.
很抱歉  我在法院有事耽搁了
So sorry. I got held up at the courthouse.
没事
No problem.
找你帮忙的人是我
You're the one doing me the favor.
先别急着谢我
Yeah, I wouldn't thank me just yet.
你什么都查不到
Oh, you couldn't find anything.
是的  地检办公室里
Nope, no one at the DA's office
没人认识叫炼金术师的人
knows anything about anybody named Alchemy.
可恶
Oh, damn.
这事
This is, um...
我猜和超能力者有关吧
Meta-human related, I assume?
-好像是的  -不妙啊
- It appears to be. - Yikes.
-我知道  -好了
- I know. - Okay.
需要帮忙就来找我  好吗
You let me know if there's anything I can do for you, yeah?
好  谢谢你把文件拿给我  塞西尔
Yeah, thanks for bringing it yourself, Cecile.
别客气
It was my pleasure.
太好了
This is really nice.
待在家里比出门舒服多了
Staying in is so much better than going out.
-对干咱们这行的人来说  是的  -没错
- When you have jobs like ours? Yes. - Yes.
怎么了
What?
你真的很帅
You're just really handsome.
你也很漂亮
You are not so bad yourself.
我以为
I thought...
我以为你不会这么早回来
I didn't think you were gonna be home for a while, right?
改变计划了
My plans changed.
真不巧  我先上楼了
Unfortunately. I'm just gonna go upstairs.
你可以喝瓶啤酒  和我们坐会
You can have a beer, sit with us.
祝你晚安
Have a good night.
我知道
I-I know.
对...  对不起
I'm... I'm sorry.
我...  能改天再续吗  还是...
I-I... should we rain check, or...
巴里  我没有因为约会被打断而不开心
Barry, I am not upset because our date got interrupted.
-我明白  -你想说什么
- That, I understand. - What do you mean?
我爸爸一进门  你就极速闪开
You, speeding away when my dad walks in.
-是啊  -因为我们在接吻吗
- Yeah. - Because, what, we're kissing?
是啊  爱瑞丝
Yeah, Iris, exactly.
难道你不想亲我吗
What, you don't want to kiss me?
我当然想亲你
Of course I want to kiss you.
但不是当着他的面
But not in front of him.
这有什么关系
What does that matter?
他是你的...  是我们的
He's your... he's our...
他是乔
Joe.
他是乔  我也不知道
Joe. I don't know.
-巴里  我们都是成年人了  -我知道
- Barry, we are adults. - I know.
-而且我们在一起  -是
- We are dating. - Yeah.
我们可以接吻的
We should be able to kiss.
同意
I agree.
好吧
Okay, yep.
你应该去和他聊聊
Yep. You should talk to him.
我  聊什么
I... about?
-真要聊吗  -是的
- For real? - Yeah.
去和他聊聊
Go talk to him.
-好吧  我去和他聊聊  -好吧
- Yeah, sure, I'll talk to him. - Okay.
-聊我们接吻的事  -好
- About us kissing. - Yeah.
一定也不会尴尬的
It's not gonna be awkward at all.
聊完了告诉我情况
Let me know how it goes.
结果肯定就是很尴尬
It's gonna be awkward, that's how.
史纳特在哪
Where's Snart?
谁在说话
Who said that?
你人在哪
Where are you?
在这呢
Boo.
斯卡德
Scudder?
史纳特在哪
Where's Snart?
我不知道
I don't know, man.
那看来我得找个知道他下落的人
Then I guess I'll just have to find someone who does.
我正好知道这么个人
And I know just the girl.
山姆·斯卡德把我扔向镜子
Yeah, Sam Scudder. He threw me into a mirror.
中城警局
我从二楼窗户摔下来
I fell out of a second-story window.
斯卡德为了找到史纳特  在追击他
So Scudder's going after everyone in Snart's old crew
以前的小队成员吗
to track him down?
但唯一的问题是
Yeah, but the only problem is,
斯卡德找不到他的
Scudder's not gonna find him.
史纳特不在了
Snart's gone.
你说他不在了是什么意思
What do you mean, he's gone?
他走了  我记得...
He's gone. I thought I--
奥利弗告诉我史纳特与
Oliver told me that Snart left
我们的一些朋友去...旅行了
with some friends of ours on a...trip.
我都不想知道
I don't even want to know.
史纳特之前的一个同伙在铁山监狱
One of Snart's old crew is at Iron Heights.
我去看看能不能和她谈谈
I'll go see if I can talk to her.
好的  我看能不能
Okay, I'll see if I can locate
去尖端科研实验室找人帮忙
any others at S.T.A.R. Labs.
实际上  抱歉  我只是...
Actually... I'm sorry, I just--
我需要和你说些事情  马上好
I need to talk to you about something really quick.
好吧  我知道
Okay, so I-I know
看到我和爱瑞丝接吻
it's probably awkward
你一定很尴尬
seeing me and Iris kiss.
-是没错  -对啊
- Uh, yeah. - Yeah.
所以我就想  也许...
So I-I was just thinking, maybe...
一定要这么尴尬吗
did it have to be awkward?
你是说像这次谈话这样吗
Do you mean like this conversation?
对  像这次谈话这样
Yeah, like this conversation.
我不知道  就是下一次你看到我们
I don't know, just 'cause the next time, um, you see us,
可能又会在你面前接吻
we may kiss again in front of you.
好吧
Okay.
所以我就想确认一下
So I just want to make sure
那个  你不会介意
that that is...okay with you.
你看  巴仔
Look, Bar.
-你是个成年人  -是的
- You're an adult. - Yes.
做你该做的事就行
Do what you got to do.
-我爱你  -我也爱你
- I love you. - I love you too.
我爱她
I love her.
我不爱看你俩亲热
I don't love watching you two make out.
好吧  还有就是
Okay, and just-just so you know,
我要告诉爱瑞丝我们谈过这事了
I am gonna tell Iris that-that we talked about this.
行  就像我说的  做你该做的
Yeah, like I said. Do what you got to do.
好的
Okay.
你对这东西能用有多大把握
How sure are you that this will work?
肯定没问题
Pretty sure.
那好  但这东西要怎么帮我们
Okay, but how's this going to help us
找到另一个哈里森·威尔斯呢
find another Harrison Wells?
你钓过鱼吗  斯诺
You ever go fishing, Snow?
-没有  -没有  好吧
- No. - No, all right.
当你去钓鱼的时候  你用鱼饵
When you go fishing, you use lures.
鱼饵引来鱼
Lures attract fish.
鱼最终咬上你的竿
Fish end up on your fishing pole.
这个卫星就是我们的钓鱼竿
This satellite is our fishing pole,
通过这个把我们非常诱人的鱼饵
through which we're going to cast our very tempting bait
投入世界上最大的海洋
out into the world's largest ocean.
怎么投
Okay, how?
怎么投  西斯科会打开一个缺口
How? Cisco will open a breach,
然后这个卫星会向多元宇宙发射
and this satellite will shootho message embedded
嵌在加强的超光速粒子激光上的信号
with a tachyon-enhanced laser out into the multiverse,
然后任何科技足够先进的地球
and any Earth that is technologically advanced enough
都应该能够接收到
should be able to receive it.
好吧  就先说这东西能运行
Okay, let's say this somehow works.
只是因为他们能解决谜题
Just 'cause they can solve a riddle
不代表他们适合这个团队
doesn't mean they're a right fit for the team.
谜题  你刚才说了谜题吗
A riddle. Did you say riddle?
-是啊  -怎么能这么说  先生
- Yeah. - How dare you, sir.
这可不是个谜题
This is not a riddle.
这是个复杂的暗码算法
This is a complex algorithmic cryptogram
设计出来测试演绎推理
designed to test deductive reasoning,
智商  问题解决能力
IQ, problem-solving skills,
以及小队消除威胁需要的所有能力
anything that our team will need to combat threats,
打击超能力者还是别的什么
meta-human or otherwise.
所以你把一个星际智商测试题
Okay, so you're just sending out an intergalactic IQ test
发给了多元宇宙中你所有的二重身
to all of your doppelgangers in the multiverse.
不仅仅是测试  把它当作是一次邀请
Not just a test. Think of it as an invitation.
当作一支精心制作的"求助"广告
Think of it as an elaborate "Help wanted" ad.
它能测试他们的态度吗
Will it test their attitudes, too?
因为我不确定能不能忍受另一个
'Cause I'm not sure I can stomach another Wells
跟你一个脾气的威尔斯
with your bedside manner.
我可在乎你了  你个屌丝
I care for you too, you jack wagon.
系统校准好了
System is calibrated.
你还在等什么
What are you waiting for?
然后...
And...
行了
That's it.
-这就行了  -对  这就行了
- That's it? - Yeah, that's it.
然后呢
So now what?
然后...
Now...
我们去吃个大贝利汉堡
we go get a Big Belly burger.
-真刺激  太快了  -我知道
- That's insane. What a rush. - I know.
我花了一段时间才习惯的
I mean, it took me a while to get used to it.
不敢相信你竟然没感到不舒服
I can't believe you're not sick at all.
我一定是有个铁打的胃
I must have an iron stomach.
好吧  你不会是想告诉我
Okay, so you're telling me
巴里从来没有带你跑过吧
that Barry has never taken you on a run?
没有
No.
那你有我真是幸运了
Well, then, I guess it's a good thing you've got me.
我想是的
Guess so.
等等
Hold up.
抱歉  我是不是对这事
I'm sorry. Am I--am I reading this,
会错情了还是什么
like, really wrong or something?
不不
No, no.
我喜欢你  杰西  就只是...
I like you, Jesse. It's just...
只是什么
It's just what?
你很快回家了
You're going home soon.
去另一个地球
To another Earth.
对了  是啊
Ah, right. Yeah.
是啊  没事  我理解
Yeah, no, it's-it's cool, yeah.
-杰西  我... -别别
- Jesse, I... - No, no, no.
完全没事的
It's--it's totally cool.
我明白
I get it.
那就...那就当朋友了
So...so friends, then?
朋友
Friends.
不过作为朋友  我是说
Well, as friends, I mean,
我们还能在城市里跑的吧
we can still run around the city, right?
当然
Sure.
长得不错啊
Good-looking guy.
作为一个罪犯来说
For a criminal.
他现在不仅仅是个罪犯了
Well, he's more than just a criminal now.
他显然是一个能穿越镜子的超能力者
Apparently, he's a meta who can travel through mirrors.
我给他起名字  叫...
I got this one. He's, uh...
-镜像大师  -什么鬼
- Mirror Master. - What the--
-比你快  -名字不错
- Boom. - That's good.
谢了  我们的地球上有个镜像大师
Thank you, we had a Mirror Master on our Earth,
叫伊万·麦克洛奇  但他不是超能力者
Evan McCulloch. Wasn't a meta, though.
他用过一种什么镜像枪
He had some kind of mirror gun that he used.
什么原理
How'd it work?
肯定用了什么转换维度的技术
Must've had dimensional warping tech
让所有东西都变成了二维的
that changed everything into two dimensions.
斯卡德正在疯狂寻找史纳特
Well, Scudder is hell-bent on finding Snart,
他在追查所有过去和史纳特有交集的人
and he's going after anybody that worked with him in the past.
乔正在审讯他们中的某个人
Joe's interviewing one of 'em right now.
所有已知的和史纳特合作的人
Well, all of Snart's known associates
不是假定死亡了就是失踪了
are either presumed dead or gone AWOL,
除了一个人
except for one.
-就是她  -罗莎琳德·狄伦
- That's her. - Rosalind Dillon.
据说她能引起严重的眩晕
Says she has the ability to induce crippling vertigo.
-她叫  -尖峰人  就像在山巅
- She's, uh-- - Top, like a top. She's the Top.
就叫这个  尖峰人  赞
That's her name. Top. Amazing.
怎样  你来起啊
What, you want to go?
行了
Okay.
那她可以让我们找到斯卡德吗
Do we think that she can lead us to Scudder?
我去看看乔从她那能问出什么
I'll have to see if Joe gets any answers out of her.
听说你前任回来了
Heard your ex is back in town.
你知道这事吗
You know anything about that?
他来找你了吗  狄伦小姐
He pay you a visit, Ms. Dillon?
这里不让人探访我这种罪犯  警探
They don't let people like me have visitors here, Detective.
整日整夜困在这个无趣的小房子里
All day, all night, in my boring little cell.
让我快发疯了呢
Makes a girl go crazy.
昨晚斯卡德试图杀害你过去的某个队友
Scudder tried to kill one of your old crewmates last night.
-里昂·威廉姆斯  -试图  真可惜没得手
- Leon Williams? - Tried? Too bad he failed.
他还会继续追杀更多人
He's gonna try to kill more.
-知道有谁吗  -告诉我们名字
- Any idea who? - Give us a name.
我就想办法让你过得舒服些
I'll see what we can do about your current situation.
好吧
Okay.
如果你改变主意了告诉我们
Let us know if you change your mind.
-抱歉  乔  -没事
- Sorry, Joe. - It's all right.
不过我还是很感谢你安排这次会面
I appreciate your setting up the interview, though.
看来我又欠你个人情
It looks like I owe you another one.
你欠的人情可越来越多了
You know, these IOUs are starting to pile up.
我有个主意
I have an idea about that.
是吗
Do you?
-斯卡德  -你想抓我
- Scudder? - You want me?
来抓啊
Come and get me.
你是说你看见斯卡德和罗莎琳德·狄伦
So you saw Sam Scudder and Rosalind Dillon
穿越玻璃窗逃出去了
escape through a glass window?
如我所说  他拉着她的手
Like I said, he grabbed her hand.
走向窗户  然后突然就不见了
They walked to the window, and then poof, they were gone.
镜子  窗户
So, mirrors, windows.
似乎只要有反射面
It sounds like he can travel through anything
他就能穿越
that has a reflective surface.
他具体是怎么做的
How exactly does he do that?
他一定是可以把爱因斯坦-罗森桥
He must be able to link Einstein-Rosen bridges
连接到任何太阳反射率高的物体吧
to anything with high solar reflectance, right?
所以他是通过反射制造虫洞
So he creates wormholes through reflections.
这可真新鲜
That's a new one.
我就不装得听懂那堆科学术语了
Look, I can't pretend to understand or care
我也不在乎  但得在发生惨剧之前
about the science of it all, but we need to find Dillon
找到狄伦和斯卡德
and Scudder before something really bad happens.
我去局里找老办法解决了
So I'm gonna go old-school at the precinct.
晚会儿见
I'll see you later.
天啊
Oh, my God.
外部有人连接进来
Pings. We got pings.
估计是你的二重身在外面
Looks like some of your doppelgangers out there
破解了你的代码  哈里
actually cracked your code, Harry.
速度可真快
That was fast.
我们去看看
Let's go take a look.
大伙  我们...
Guys? We're...
老爸看起来很好啊
Dad seems fine.
不  他还是有点担心的
Yeah, no, he's still a little weird about it.
不过你和他谈过了  对吧
You talked to him, though, right?
是的
Yeah, I did.
会没事的
Yeah, it'll be good.
好的  挺好
Okay, great.
-那我们晚上见  -好
- Then I'll see you tonight. - All right.
你选个好看的电影哦
You'll pick a good movie?
-我尽量  -好的
- I'll try. - Okay.
我也尽量找找那个超能力者
I'm also gonna try to find our meta-humans
显然现在没人管这事了
that apparently no one else cares about right now.
你到底去哪里了
Where the hell did you go?
我要告诉你几遍  罗莎
How many times do I have to tell you, Rosa?
我被困在这里了
I was stuck in there.
不管我被什么击中了  反正有超能力了
Whatever it was that hit me gave me this crazy ability.
在我看来  这都是昨晚才发生的
And to me, all this just happened last night.
已经三年了  山姆
It's been three years, Sam.
有很多事情已经不一样了
So many things are different now.
你也被击中了  对不对
You were hit too, weren't you?
你也和我一样有超能力了吗
You can do things like me?
-对  -给我看看
- Yeah. - Show me.
那你最好抓紧了
You might want to hold onto something.
看到没  山姆
See, Sammy?
有太多东西已经改变了
Too much has changed.
那我们就改变回去
Then let's change it back.
我可以阻止史纳特  罗莎
I can stop Snart, Rosa.
我们可以阻止史纳特
We...can stop Snart.
史纳特  他不在了
Snart? He's gone.
早就不在了
Long gone.
那我们就夺下这座城市
Then let's take this city.
我们现在想做什么都可以
We can be who we want to now.
我们能掌控一切
We can be in control.
现在城市里没有人能阻止我们了
There's no one in this city who can stop us now.
还有一个人能
There's one person who can.
谁
Who?
闪电侠
The Flash.
你好啊
Well, hey, now.
我破解了你们发出的导数信号
I-I solved the derivative you done beamed up.
我叫威尔斯  哈里森·威尔斯
My name is Wells, Harrison Wells.
你们可以叫我地狱威尔斯
You can call me Hell's Wells.
我这个称号源于我的过去
They call me that 'cause of my past.
现在不方便跟你们细说
I won't get into it with you now right and proper.
我得去赶马车了
I'd like to hitch wagons and--
晚饭吃得不好
I had a bad dinner.
-换  -好
- Pass. - All right.
这是地球十七
This is Earth-17.
再联系
I'll be in touch.
多元宇宙的各位  你们好
Salutations to all of you out there in the multiverse.
我最近不知为何收到
I have of late, wherefore I know not, received a communiqué
"盛世地球"市民的公报
from the citizens of Terra-Prime.
"盛世地球"
Terra-Prime?
-智障  -换
- Nerd. - Pass.
大家好  我是哈里森·威尔斯
Bonjour. Moi, je suis Harrison Wells.
小丑不可信
You can't trust a mime.
-有道理  -换
- Can't argue with that. - Pass.
好了  三个都不行
Okay, guys. We're 0 for 3 now.
这是最后一个了
This is our last one.
他来自地球十九
It's coming from Earth-19.
大家好啊
Hello, hello, hello.
多元宇宙的各位  你们好
Hello, out there in the multiverse,
也不知道你们是谁
whoever you may be.
你们的密码让我破解得很爽啊
I really enjoyed cracking the cryptogram you broadcast.
小把戏真有意思
I like the cute trick,
在原始数据串中
embedding the secondary measures
嵌入辅助措施  聪明
in the primary data string. It's clever.
多数人都接收不到
Most people wouldn't have caught it.
重要的是  我接收到了
I caught it. But that's the point.
我想你们需要个聪明人
You need a genius, I guess,
帮助你们打击
to help you in your fight
那些可怕的超能力者
against these awful meta-hominids.
我得告诉你们  告诉我自己
Well, I got to tell you-- I got to tell you, to me,
听着很有趣
that sounds like fun.
我把我的简历发给你们吧
So...I'll enclose my curriculum vitae.
你们都知道我们语言相通
You already know we speak the same language.
先看看  再跟我说你们的想法
But take a look. Tell me what you think.
下次见面再聊
Until our next communion.
我咋能这么无礼呢
Oh, where are my manners?
谢谢
Thank you.
-不错  -很不错
- Not bad. - Not bad at all.
哈里
Harry?
-换  -什么
- Pass. - What?
-换  -等等  等等
- Pass. - Wait, what? Wait a minute.
这家伙破解了密码  他有心帮忙
That guy cracked the code, and he wants to do it.
他人不错  又不坏
And he's nice, and he's not evil.
结合了我们已知的威尔斯的所有特点
And that's a combination of Wells we haven't had thus far.
我这辈子都靠我的直觉
All my life, everyone I've ever hired to work for me,
招人来帮忙
I have trusted my gut.
直觉告诉我这人不行
My gut tells me that's not the guy.
接着找
Keep looking.
苍天啊
Oh, for God's sake.
好了  听我说
Okay, you know what?
我受不了了
I can't take this anymore.
什么
What?
我还以为你们已经聊过我俩的事了
I thought you guys were supposed to talk about us.
聊了
We did.
那你干嘛还那么别扭
Then why are you being so weird?
我没有
I'm not.
爸
Dad?
爱瑞丝
Iris.
我跟他说了  如果你俩想依偎一起
I already told him, if you two want to cuddle,
想亲热  或别的什么
make out, do whatever,
我都...不介意的
I-I-I...go for it.
我不介意的
I don't care.
巴里
Barry?
我们是不是该回避一下
Should we give you guys a minute?
-对  -不  没事
- Yeah. - No, no, it's fine.
巴里  这不再是我爸的原因了
Look, Barry, this isn't about my dad anymore.
他都不介意了
He's fine with it.
我没有完全不介意
I'm not totally fine with it.
你怎么还觉得别扭呢
So why do you have a problem with this?
谢天谢地
Thank God.
第一国家银行发生抢劫
There's a robbery at First National.
-嫌犯是斯卡德和狄伦  -斯卡德和狄伦
- Suspects match Scudder and Dillon's description.- Scudder and Dillon
-抱歉  我得走了  -走吧
- Yeah, I'm sorry, I got to go. - Okay.
我也去帮你吧
Hey...let me help.
养兵千日  用兵一时  对吧
We've been training for a reason, right?
-让我试试吧  -好  走吧
- I've got to try. - Yeah, all right, cool.
-听我指示  -好
- Just follow my lead. - Okay.
继续干下去
We keep this up,
宝贝  咱们就衣食无忧了
baby, we'll be set for life.
那还等什么
Then what are you waiting for?
再干一票
Let's do it again.
为你在所不辞  宝贝
Anything for you, baby.
对啊  那就不能让你们带着东西离开
Yeah, so we're not gonna let you leave here with that.
闪电侠
Hey, Flash.
久仰大名
Heard a lot about you.
很好啊
That's great.
这位就没怎么听过了
Can't say the same for you, though.
我是杰西·快客
The name's Jesse Quick.
抱歉  斯卡德
So...I'm sorry, Scudder,
你这偷盗勾当到此为止
but your little crime spree, it's gonna have to end here.
我想这事由不得你来定
Oh, I don't think you have much of a say in it.
我想拿什么就拿什么
I'm gonna take whatever I want.
还以为你在找莱昂纳多·史纳特
I thought you were looking for Leonard Snart.
何苦呢  他的威风不再
Why bother? His reign is over.
城里已另立新王
There's a--a new king in town.
而我是王后
And I'm the queen.
这我就不确定了
Yeah, I wouldn't be too sure about that.
我确定  小姑娘
Oh, I would, little girl.
他们去哪了
Where'd they go?
那边
There.
待在这
Stay here.
我没开玩笑
I'm not kidding.
裙子不错  尖峰人
Nice skirt, Top.
尖峰人[也指陀螺]
Top.
我喜欢
I like it.
因为它们会旋转  旋转  旋转
Because they spin, spin, spin.
什么  怎么回事
What? What's happening?
我失去平衡了
I can't get my balance.
我知道  没事的
I know. It's okay.
你不会有事的
You're gonna be okay.
但是你就有事了
But you won't.
祝你们能成功把他救出来
Good luck getting him out.
巴里
Barry!
-发生什么了  -我不知道
- What happened? - I don't know.
我不知道  我看了狄伦一眼
I don't know, okay? I looked at Dillon,
然后就失去了平衡了
and I lost my balance.
她是个超能力者
She's a meta-human
引发了眩晕
who induces vertigo.
她直接就让你失去平衡了
She just whammied you.
我猜是这样的吧
Yeah, I guess so.
现在说这些都没意义了
It doesn't really matter, does it?
全都是因为我  现在巴里被困在了那里
Because now Barry's trapped in there and it's because of me.
你知道吗  我
Well, you know, I--
我去和她谈谈
I'll go talk to her.
他在说什么
What is he saying?
是某种镜像语吗
Is that some sort of mirror language?
镜子显现出的是相反的事物
Mirrors show objects in reverse.
也许我们听到的就是这个
Maybe that's what we're hearing here.
只有一个验证的方法
Only one way to find out.
西斯科  你在找什么
What are you looking for, Cisco?
你们看过《双峰》吗
You ever seen "Twin Peaks"?
《双峰》是1990年由大卫·林奇
导演的美国系列电视剧
肯定没看过  问也白问
Of course not. Why do I ask?
这是一种逆录音的手法
This is an old backmasking trick
在剧中的外星人角色身上使用过
they used for The Man from Another Place,
他们把他的音频倒着录下来
where they record his audio backwards
然后正着播放出来
and then play it forwards.
就像是奥兹·奥斯朋的唱片
Like the Ozzy Osbourne records.
就是这个意思
Sure, let's go with that.
巴里  说几句话吧
Okay, Barry, say something.
再说一遍
Say it again.
快把我弄出去
Get me out of here.
现在能听懂你的话了
Now we can understand you.
我们如何把他救出来
How do we get him out of there?
巴里  你试过穿出来吗
Barry, have you tried to phase out yet?
试过了  不行
Yes. It's not working.
如果斯卡德把镜子用作虫洞的话
If Scudder used this mirror as a wormhole,
那么这些分子就处于超流动状态  所以
then these molecules are in a hyper state of flux, so all--
我们需要非常寒冷的东西使其降速
We need is something really cold to slow them down.
我可以帮忙  我们走吧
I can help with that. Let's go.
陪陪他
Keep him company.
你不要那个了吗
Aren't you gonna need that?
有什么意义呢
What's the point?
我以为我准备好了  看来我还没有
You know, I thought I was ready, but clearly I'm not.
杰西  你不能这么自责
Jesse, you can't blame yourself for this.
-发生在巴里身上的事  -全是我的错
- What happened to Barry-- - It was totally my fault.
他让我留在后面  但是我没有听
I mean, he told me to stay back, but I didn't listen, you know?
我就盲目地往前跑
I just ran in blind, and,
现在他被困在了里面
now he's stuck, so--
听着  你是犯了错  那又怎样呢
Look, you made a mistake. So what?
我敢肯定巴里最开始肯定也犯了不少错
I mean, I'm sure Barry made a lot of mistakes at first too.
不要让这些事摧毁了你的信心
Don't let this destroy your confidence.
你命中注定是要做这个的  杰西
You're meant to do this, Jesse.
你命中注定就是个极速者
You're meant to be a speedster.
所以你才有这些超能力  而我没有
That's why you have these powers and I don't.
你说这些只是想让我振作起来
You're just trying to cheer me up.
我知道你说过不想和我约会  所以
I know you said you don't want to hang, so--
不  我说不想去约会是因为我很害怕
No, I said I didn't want to hang out because I was scared.
因为你是住在另外一个地球的  但是
Because you live on another Earth, but
我意识到我再也不想因此而害怕了
I realized I don't want to be scared of that anymore.
我觉得这个没用
I don't think it's gonna work.
你觉得这个没用是什么意思
What do you mean, you don't think it's gonna work?
我设计的这个能达到绝对零度
I built this to go to absolute zero.
这我知道  但是我们需要镜子
I realize that. But we need the mirror
在足够长的时间里维持零点能
to maintain zero-point energy long enough
好让巴里的分子能穿过来
for Barry's molecules to pass through it.
绝对零度已经足够冷了
Absolute zero's more than cold enough to do that.
通常情况下是的  但是我们还要考虑
Normally, but we have to account for the internal energy
镜子分子的内能
of the mirror's molecules, as well.
所以虽然绝对零度是能达到的最低温度
So while absolute cold might be the lowest possible temperature,
-它却不是  -却不是能达到的
- it's not the-- - It's not the lowest
-最低的焓  -没错
- enthalpy state possible. - Exactly right.
焓是物体的一个热力学能状态函数  即热函
那我们怎么办
So what are we gonna do?
我现在还不知道
I don't know...yet.
跟上我的思路
Okay, go with me here.
我们能不能把这个拿给另外一个威尔斯
What if we send this to the other Wells
看他能不能想出什么好办法
and see if he can figure something out?
-好主意  -什么  不行
- Yeah. - What? No.
所以现在每个人都是可替代的  是吗
What? Oh, everybody's replaceable now, is that right?
-是不是这样  -你瞎说什么
- Is that what this is? - What are you talking about?
是你瞎说什么  你不就是这么说的吗
What are you talking about? That's what you said.
我不是这么说的  我说的是我们需要
That's not what I said. I'm saying we need to figure out
找出解决问题的方法  时间不等人
a solution to this problem, and time's not on our side right now.
这没用的
That's not gonna help. You're
你说的根本没用  反而越弄越糟
not contributing to the problem. You're making things worse.
-你知道我怎么想的吗  -你怎么想的
- You know what I think? - What do you think?
我觉得你不喜欢
I think you don't like the idea
有人替代你的位置
of someone taking your place here.
你胡说什么
What are you talking about?
所以你才不喜欢另外一个威尔斯
This is why you don't like the other Wells.
你说什么呢  这还是我的主意啊
What are you talking about? It was my idea.
这并不代表你喜欢这个主意呀
But that doesn't mean you have to like it.
跟喜不喜欢没关系  好吗
It's got nothing to do with liking, okay?
你知道什么是有关系的吗
You know what it has to do with?
-分子减速器  -分子减速器
- A molecular decelerator. - A molecular decelerator.
如果我们把分子减速器装在
If we augment the molecular decelerator
冷冻枪的低温发生器上使其增强威力的话
on the cryogenic generator of the cold gun--
我能做出来  我能做出来
I can build that. I can build that.
棒极了
Great.
你在做什么
What are you doing?
这条裤子是不是显得我屁股很大
Do these pants make my butt look big?
我现在是真的困在了镜子里了
I'm literally stuck in a mirror.
抱歉
Sorry, yeah.
镜子里是什么样的
What's it like in there?
很黑
dark.
爱瑞丝  我
Look, Iris, I'm...
我很抱歉我现在被困住了
I'm sorry that I'm... stuck right now.
亲爱的  我知道你困在了里面
Oh, honey, I know that you're stuck.
没关系的  我们会把你救出来
It's okay, we are gonna get you out of there.
不  我不是这个意思
No, I mean--no.
让你误解了
That was misleading.
不是指这个镜子  而是我们
Not the mirror. I mean, with us.
乔的事情  你是对的
This thing with Joe, and you were right.
确实不是乔的问题  是我的问题
I mean, it's not Joe. It's me. It's my problem.
对于我们仨之间
I've just been feeling nervous
这种新的关系
about this new dynamic
我觉得很紧张
between the three of us.
我不清楚
I-I don't know.
现在我拥有曾经梦寐以求的一切
I have everything that I have ever wanted right now.
这些我之前从未拥有过
And I've never had that in my life.
在很多方面
In a lot of ways,
比起一无所有的状态我更害怕了  因为
it's scarier than having nothing, because...
更容易失败了
it's easier to fail than succeed.
而我很想成功
And I really want to succeed.
你现在在笑什么呢
What could you possibly be laughing about right now?
抱歉  巴里
I am so sorry, Barry.
你太贴心了
You are really sweet.
但是通过镜子和扬声器
But it is weird talking to you
和你说话太奇怪了
through a mirror and a speaker,
而我现在很想吻你
and I really want to kiss you right now.
我们可以以后再谈这些吗
But can we please talk about this later?
好  以后再谈
Yeah. We can talk about it later.
估计是挺怪的
Guess it is pretty weird.
就好像我在这里  又不在这里
It's like I'm here, but I'm not.
怎么了
What?
我刚想到一个阻止斯卡德的方法
I just thought of a way to stop Scudder.
这是什么
What is that?
这能帮我们把他从那里弄出来
This is how we get him out of there.
太好了  来吧
All right. Let's do it.
好啦
Okay.
现在试试
Try it now.
这只有华氏零下280度
It's only negative 280 degrees Fahrenheit.
得变得更冷才行
We got to get it colder somehow.
我以为你们说过这玩意儿
I thought you guys said this thing
能把他弄出来
could get him out of there.
这个装置
Okay, this thing
是非常高级的分子减速器
is a highly advanced molecular decelerator
由低温发动机供能
that's being powered by a cryo-engine,
半小时前我们即兴制造出来的
and we just kind of improvised it in the last 30 minutes,
拜托奏效吧
so let's just--just cut us some slack, please?
再试试  巴里
Just keep trying, Barry.
超能力者警报
Meta-human alert.
天呐
Oh, for God's sake.
如果不是同一个
If it's not one thing...
那就是另外一个
It's the other.
坚持住  巴仔
Hold on, Bar.
大伙们
Guys?
人呢
Hello?
中城市政银行被抢了
Central City Municipal Bank just got robbed.
我猜猜是谁干的
Let me guess by who.
大伙们
Guys.
-巴里  -嘿
- Barry. - Hey.
-怎么出来的  -一会再说吧
- How? - Let's figure it out later.
现在我们需要阻止斯卡德和狄伦
Right now we need to stop Scudder and Dillon.
我们该怎么做
Okay, so--so what do we do?
用镜子
We're gonna use mirrors,
一个老把戏  还有一个老朋友
an old trick, and an old friend.
-谁啊  -史纳特
- Yeah? - It's Snart.
听说你们回城里了
I heard you were back in town.
-史纳特  -斯卡德  罗莎
- Snart? - Scudder, Rosa.
好久不见
Long time.
还不够久
Not long enough.
别过来
Hang back.
这家伙欠我的
This guy owes me.
你找我们来
So you called us.
想要什么
The hell you want?
同一件事
Same thing.
你们俩  离开这里
You two, gone.
现在形势变了
Things have changed.
现在这是我们的城市了
This is our town now.
-是吗  -是的
- Is that right? - Yeah, it is.
你的小小冷冻枪
And that little cold gun of yours
这次可救不了你了
isn't gonna save you from me.
这个可不一定
We'll see about that, now, won't we?
砰
Bang!
全息图还真有趣啊
Funny thing about holograms.
它们不过是真家伙的微弱映像
They're just pale reflections of the real deal.
又相见了
Hello again.
杰西·快客
Jesse Quick.
跑得快  摔得也快
Quick to run, quick to fall.
学得也快
Quick to learn.
玩得好  闪电侠
Well played, Flash.
-怎么了  -我明白了  好吗
- What? - I know, right?
这是德罗斯特效应
This is the, uh, Droste effect.
递归的一种视觉形式
指一张图片的某个部分与整张图片相同
如此产生无限循环
你肯定听说过  对吧
I'm sure you've heard of it, right?
是一种无限反射循环
It's an infinite reflective loop
甚至你都无法逃脱
that even you can't escape.
祝你挣脱成功
Good luck getting out.
所以你确定他无法
So you're sure he can't
通过镜像大师的方法越狱吗
Mirror Master his way out of this cell?
是的  不可能
No, it's impossible.
牢房的每一寸都用
Every inch has been modified
防反射材料改造过了
with an anti-reflective material.
甚至斯卡德过阵子都会忘记自己的容貌
Even Scudder's gonna forget what he looks like after a while.
我得走了
Well, I should go.
谢谢你做的一切
Hey. So, thank you for everything.
不  谢谢你才对
Oh, no. Thank you.
我们又抓住了一个坏蛋超能力者
We got another bad meta right where he belongs.
-没错  -乔
- Yep, all right. - Hey, Joe.
我们之间有太多的亏欠了
We have an awful lot of IOUs.
不如今晚一起吃顿晚餐吧
Do you maybe want to grab some dinner tonight?
-晚餐  -是的
- Dinner? - Yeah.
我今晚要和孩子们
Yeah, I-- well, I've got movie night
一起看电影
with my kids tonight.
改天再约如何
Rain check?
当然可以
Yeah. Of course.
那就下次
Another time, then.
什么情况呀
What was that about?
-你怎么不直接答应呢  -不知道
- Why didn't you just say yes? - I don't know.
紧张的不止你一个
You're not the only one that gets nervous around here.
我从来没震过18个维度
You guys, I've never vibed across 18 dimensions before.
再坚持一会儿
Just a little bit longer.
你们好  地球人
Greetings, earthlings.
开玩笑的  我不这样说话
Just kidding. I don't really talk like that.
我一直想这么说
I've just always wanted to say that.
地球人
Earthlings.
幽默的威尔斯  这倒新鲜
Wells with a sense of humor. That's new.
神枪手
Hey, sharpshooter.
你
You.
你很帅
You're... handsome.
我知道
I know.
-你也是  -当然
- Likewise, I'm sure. - Yeah.
哈里森
Harrison.
你可以叫我HR
You can call me HR.
那就HR
HR it is.
这是我们的团队
This is the team, then. Um...
这是西斯科·拉蒙  无所不能
This is Cisco Ramon. He can do anything.
好的
Okay.
她是凯特琳·斯诺博士
This is Dr. Caitlin Snow.
-她相当聪明  -嗨  -单身
- She is brilliant. - Hi. - Single.
-别...  这是我女儿
- Don't--all right, that's my daughter.
你不用握手
You don't have to shake her hand.
那个小伙儿是沃利·韦斯特
That gentleman there is Wally West.
这是巴里·艾伦
This is Barry Allen, or
或者被称为这个地球的
as we call him on this Earth...
闪电侠
The Flash.
欢迎来到地球一
Welcome to Earth-1.
谢谢  地球一  这样说好奇怪
Thanks. Earth-1, that's weird.
好了  不用客气了
Okay, well, we don't have to stand on ceremony.
我们不用再次伤心道别了吧  伙计们
We don't have to go through all the tears again, do we, gang? Right?
上次你走时我哭了吗
Well, did I-- did I cry last time you left?
-我在说自己  -明白了
- I was talking about myself. - Oh, gotcha.
听着
Hey, listen.
别担心
Don't worry about it, okay?
只有一个哈里
There's only one Harry.
正要告诉你
Oh, I wanted to tell you.
分子减速器没起作用
The molecular decelerator, it wasn't working.
这是怎么回事
Okay, what does that mean?
这说明我们没能把巴里拉出镜子
It means that we did not get Barry out of that mirror.
不是我们
It wasn't us.
那是谁
Then who did it?
你说呢
You tell me.
-回头见  -好的
- See you later. - Yeah.
地球二有优秀的极速者保护了
Earth-2's gonna have one hell of a speedster protecting it.
名师出高徒
Well, I did learn from the best.
如果你要我帮忙  你知道怎么回来
If you ever need any help, you know how to get back.
明白  我会回来的
Yeah. Yeah, definitely, I'll be back.
好吧
All right.
你们
Okay, you guys.
准备好了吗
Ready?
好了
Yeah, yeah.
西斯科
Okay, Cisco.
旧的不去  新的不来
Out with the old, in with the new.
你从来不会是旧的  哈里
You'll never be old to us, Harry.
-准备好了  -是的
-Ready? - Yeah.
开始吧
Okay, let's do this.
还有件事  我走后  千万不要
Oh, one more thing. While I'm gone, never, ever,
无论如何
no matter what--
他要说什么
What--what was he gonna say?
我们都在想  "他要说什么"
And we're all like, "What was he gonna say?"
好了  我饿死了
That's cool, though. I'm starving.
你们这儿有大贝利汉堡店吗
Do you guys have Big Belly Burger?
有的东西从来不变
Some things never change.
饿坏了
Famished.
巴里有提到
Did Barry say anything about
我和塞西尔的尴尬时刻吗
this embarrassing moment with Cecile?
第一次见新威尔斯怎么样
How did your first meeting go with the new Wells?
不错  我觉得他还不错
Good. Yeah, I think he'll work out fine.
这样好  期待见到他
Oh, good. I look forward to meeting him.
-悠着点  -怎么了
- Whoa. - What?
开玩笑的
I'm just kidding.
说实话
I got to be honest,
我得花点时间接受
it's gonna take a bit for me to get used to that.
实际上有件事想和你们说
I actually have something to run by you guys that
-也许可以避免尴尬  -真的
- I think might help with that. - Really?
-是啊  -什么事
- Yeah. - What up?
我一直在想  也许对大家都好
Well, I've just been thinking that maybe for all of us--
我应该  大概
that I should probably, um...
搬出去
get my own place.
-真的  -是的
- Really? - Yeah.
你们怎么看
What do you think?
-我同意  -我以为你永远不走了呢
- I say yes. - I thought you'd never leave.
-没开玩笑  -爸爸
- Seriously? - Dad.
-天呐  -巴仔
- Wow. - Look, Bar, come on.
我会想你的  但是吧
I'm gonna miss you, but damn.
你都成年了  是时候了
You grown. About time.
我搞不清是我自己想走的
I can't tell if I'm leaving
还是被赶出家门了
or if I'm getting kicked out.
随你怎么想
You feel like you feel.
我觉得是被赶出去的
Feel like I'm getting kicked out.
我也觉得你是被赶走的
I mean, yeah, I feel like you're getting kicked out too.
很明显嘛
Like, it's pretty obvious
你被赶走了
you're getting kicked out.
爸爸
Dad.
你成年了
You're grown.
好吧
Oh, well. Cool.